yo listen Hoshi listen bro you're on the
junkyard love podcast a man finally it's
about time it's damn about time it's in
perfect timing that's hey oh yeah
shading man I'm super glad to have you
here thank you I'm excited to be here
he's been too long yeah I'm at weight
actually before we even just do this
introduction let's this pump these beers
and just use it okay so I mean I'm happy
to have you on here and talk about your
career and who you are like as a rapper
and as a person but that's the dopest
thing about this it's like I don't have
any management like I don't have anybody
tell me what to do like your management
is my homies right so we get a just
drink a beer and just [__] man like
we just we just get a get comfy and get
to know you like there's no I don't know
man it's just pumped like I'm just
pumped I get to catch up with my homies
when they're in town when they're
exactly exactly I get you know we're
gonna do it on a professional though
yeah well [__] bro um let's let's take
it from let's take it from from the
young ages so you're you're a rapper
let's just start with that people who
haven't heard of Hoshi will link the
info in the comments of course but but
so all you know right now listener is
this man's a rapper sitting across from
me give me it give me a little bit your
story membrillo I mean I grew up in Co
so came from Co so high school grew up
just has a little punk-ass skater kid I
was always pretty smart and stuff just
had like my own way about it I don't
want to do it like the standard way or
help however I was supposed to do it I
didn't want to do it that way I don't
like I was always just pushing against
the grain trying to just have my fun but
like create a life where I could be free
and it more than anything just like my
freedom is like my biggest thing I
wanted to be able to do what I want and
have a good time and like see the people
I love smile so this I was always
thinking I was gonna be a pro skater
just in dude any some wild something
yeah anything crazy that I just thought
that that was gonna be it because I
didn't want to do it how I was supposed
to do it right so growing up I was
always like dreaming and scheming and
I've been writing songs since I was like
but I mean that was like that was the
one thing that I wouldn't say I was
gonna because I knew my dad would kill
me if I was like you know what that I
figured it out I'm gonna be a rock star
this tight little pants to hear that
yeah I just I just like wrote but I just
didn't think about it and then
eventually it was like I was just
writing because I had like all this
stuff in my mind because I've always
been like it I don't sleep like not
sleeper I'll just be sitting thinking or
do I just overthinking like analyze and
think about every situation in life and
like we were just talking before this
about how we both seem to see things
like as a whole like you know right
there's the individual parts but there's
someone who's kind of up above was like
okay this is oh the chess player another
chess you know exactly so I've always
just like analysed and think and like
try to put everything together but I
just seem to do it through the nights of
sleeping it's like it just turned into
like me writing songs because I had all
these feelings and ideas and stuff like
about what the hell was going on and
what my idea of it and then yeah then it
just turned into like singing it and
yeah people start listening people
people feel like that I guess what would
you do so when you first started
actually like recording it did you just
what programming is remember uh the firm
the first time I ever recorded ever was
we had like this my computer actually
didn't even end up working well I rented
a hotel because I was living in my
friend's basement with my other hold are
you this like barely eighteen okay like
I was living in my friend's basement
with like two other people and so like
I've finally got all the money to get
all the recording gear [__] but like we
couldn't record there obviously there's
our trash and stuff so we took and I
rented a hotel room for like two nights
so that we could record for the first
time ever and see what happened perfect
and we got there
and it didn't work like I I could like
we're running off like some punk ass
program that we try to her if all things
that it didn't work out a whole lot of
[__] that can go wrong
right so then Eric came through and
brought its MacBook so we ended up
recording in GarageBand and I made my
first song ever that night and it was
called I think it was called like tell
me to stop or something like that
it's not out is it no it's so old it was
long how is it like give you this you
know I don't know if I heard that long
time but it's still the same attitude
like it was it was just about it was
like if you tell me to stop and I want
to tell you know something like thank
you like you know sometimes that shit's
tight though and it's enough to kind of
get the emotion it's not so much about
that's something I love about hip-hop is
it's not so much about what what they're
saying that sometimes like a lot of
times it is about what you're saying
right a lot of times you know the fill
words is the the frequencies man like
the the vibe the you know even just like
if someone was humming like mixed in
like so like like it was like a single
like basic track but I remember we was
in the hotel room just like ragin in
there laughter like it was the best [__]
we could well you got to do though you
got to do that you got a you got a hyper
set up that's always been one of my
problems actually is I don't know how to
like tell if my songs actually good like
if I should drop it
because I like every song that has been
like one of my better songs like wake up
and I loved yeah yeah but like wake up
and there's a couple other ones like I
did not like it I didn't want to drop it
like I was I wasn't going to drop it and
then like Angelou or one of my brothers
or something about like no this is the
one dude like you gotta you gotta let
that go
cuz like me I don't know like a lot of
my music I really just like to like sing
about what I'm feeling or like emotional
[__] I don't know if you go like this
yeah I just like to like seeing some
stuff and then like I'll just sit in
there and just listen to like what I
sang like if I die tomorrow like some of
my emotions sometimes I just sit there
and just like I didn't know if it was
good or not it was just what I needed to
hear
so I was like
it just feels amazing like I don't like
see that's the secret though that's how
you dig out in your mind the real [__]
you know that's right that's why people
feel what you pick up what you're
[__] putting down I guess so yeah so
okay so so you mentioned your brothers
you have two brothers right yeah okay so
back up a little bit for your eighteen
what's your life like before before
you're eighteen what's your childhood
like you won't talk about that um girl
will my parents
okay I had some some dope-ass parents
yes yeah yeah it was always trying to
teach us kind of like my mindset you
know my dad always wanted me to like to
do good things and be a good person but
more than anything you always just
taught me like to just good whatever you
gonna do just do it a hundred percent I
like the business don't half-ass it
don't don't cheat yourself in life like
if you're gonna go for it just do it
like what do you mean try like why would
you try to do it she's gonna try it like
just do it isn't like that I mean it was
it's kind of like rough I skate
what do you mean dad like this [__] is
so hard
were you in sports or anything like it
yeah I wrestled but like the sports I
loved I loved like snowboarding or
skating right [__] like that which I
mean is more expensive to go up to the
mountain of snowboard all the time but
like skateboarding and like riding bikes
and stuff like that like I really like
motocross and [__] I just like going
fast I mean like sports like are cool
but it was always just kind of boring
for me and I'm not like bald coordinated
type deal like you ain't ball
coordinated yeah that ain't me like I
just like to go really fast right just
meshing down a mountain yeah my favorite
things to do is I mean so I'm not seeing
super on speed and more flow person yeah
so like it never really got me wiggling
you know to like bomb a hill on a
skateboard just going straight down but
I did love hitting the hill on a
skateboard in my headphones and weaving
through sorry I was just five and just
trying to like be something the same
thing on the snow
oh yeah that's what that's kind of me
too it's like everybody knows I like to
smoke so like skating I'll just be
cruising through the bowl shredding oh
yeah have you been skating a lot another
year you live in Arizona now you've been
skating I was getting a lot more but is
it so hot when yeah it's really hot yeah
something I couldn't imagine man I would
I'd be complaining for the first like
three weeks like I don't know I mean it
was something else then in the middle of
the summertime
literally like 115 degrees for like a
month and a half straight yeah every day
if you eat [__] you also get burnt yeah
if the ground is like burning hot
literally the floor is lava but there's
no warm-up for it like you wake up in
the morning walk out to your car at nine
o'clock in the morning it's already a
hundred and eight degrees outside pretty
cold
it doesn't even make any sense is why
this is way too hot I mean but so you
grew up it being able to snowboard and
skateboard here cuz you're from here
over the Pacific runs west yeah it was
beautiful
yeah very beautiful man so back when
you're skateboarding and [__] like were
you close with your brothers when your
girl oh definitely those are like my
brother my two little brothers close
those are my best friends in the whole
world forever like that's our like we
kind of grew up like I don't how our own
house like a little bit away from people
and [__] is like obviously we had hella
friends and stuff but we just always
walked together and it was like whether
it was at the skate park or doing
whatever was doing was it always
together like that and that was a gang
is just like and I mean obviously our
forensic or wedding [__] but yeah that's
great yeah that's a cool thing I mean I
feel like what I see from just like an
outside perspective looking at you three
it seems like you know obviously you
know you're the oldest you the leader
right but so you guys sometimes be the
wise guys make you make this like super
thing is the thing is you make this like
- hey together like - alone we you know
we're kind of [__] you know crazy but
together you know we can we can put our
heads to some [__] and definitely yeah
I know that I'm sure they probably do do
a lot of you do we're talking on the way
up here about about one of your brothers
he's doing the music - definitely
definitely baby and they just dropped
ps4
oh yeah yeah I saw that logo for the
thumbnail I haven't watched yep check
that one super dope Andrew actually
filmed it yeah yeah so it's very crazy
what's what's Andy's film GH drew sign I
believe on Instagram how to make sure we
mention him and he's gonna treat him
good yup and stuff to watch him to watch
him blossom you know definitely so the
the branch through growing up I mean on
the way here we were talking about like
just like getting reckless in like
avoiding pain you know a lot of your
lyrics come through and then and that's
that's the realness and we've got to
dive into that so can you talk about
like you know like recently you saying
your brother which is kind of neat just
doing better now too you know oh
definitely yeah you know forward going
straight yeah you were telling me you
were doing some stupid [__] to you just
doing a little bit better now yes tell
me about this mindset me like what was
going on what's happening now what I
mean
Tommy's like seven she I mean we had a
really cool life and everything with our
parents and and being close together and
stuff but that doesn't mean it wasn't
crazy and like hectic you know to take
some time so I mean a lot of life
growing up was like a lot of mayhem and
everything behind the scenes of it being
really dope and then it turned into me
later like so I mean late seventeen
through my 22 I'm like out there by
myself really trying to figure [__] out
like trying to get music under going
when I'm living with friends trying to
like figure out money stuff like that my
parents were really going through a hard
time my dad got sick and I couldn't work
anymore you had like a spinal disease
and stuff like that and then so I mean
it was really it was we was all for our
own for a minute and like trying to
figure it out so I started getting
harder and harder trying to piece it
together we're trying to get studio
pieces you know do anything we can just
to try to and make the dream happen it
like it's even more stressful because as
things are falling apart people are like
you should be getting like jobs and
stuff that's actually gonna guarantee
you bringing money and the moisture us
was getting we're all going no not we're
gonna believe in this even more because
this half Stephen won't like it has to
work like so so much that you got to
push through in a small town man exactly
so it just turned into a lot of
craziness and using things to try to not
have to feel [__] and you know what not
about our vices exactly exactly and I
mean a lot of it was fun and it was ups
and downs and everything trying to try
to vibe to it and then finally getting
music to work yeah we're on tour we're
going crazy having a great time I'm like
you finally like feel like hey maybe
like I could I will bring something home
and like let him know that maybe we're
gonna be good like and then like the the
night before I've supposed to come home
on tour pops passes away like on some
free [__] so that just that kind of just
put all of us I mean going from like one
of the highest highs that I personally
ever been at just being on tour and like
finally feeling like I mean we're
connected with a label we're like
there's like contracts on the table like
this is like a dream come true this is
literally everything that they said that
we weren't gonna do and like for some
reason it's actually happening and then
like in the same night of walking
offstage from my sold-out shows and [__]
to get like the phone call and be like
hey you know like your superhero is gone
now so like you gotta come figure this
out it was just like all of us kind of
just like hit a spiral you know trying
to diss mmm Tran just bras yeah just
trying to process it and then avoid it
too you know yeah run from it and deal
with it at the same time and then at the
same time also like being and put like
right back on the tour afterwards and I
mean that's what I wanted because I was
like we can't stop but you know it's not
an option so like yeah you know props to
you for real for hey thank you
you know I mean you know what I mean you
got to be strong through those things
and it gives other people around us the
strength you know process exactly but I
mean like the hard part of it is being
like going back to toy then I'm away
from my brothers again and my mom and
stuff so like trying to like take care
of each other but like through through
the distance and you know be there and
it was a lot of stuff you know my
brother's going through school and was
it like at the point of graduating and
going through all this [__]
it was just it was just a lot of mayhem
you know and then this is you know and
what pops going I'm supposed to be the
leader you know like taking care of the
house and [__] and I'm not even there
because I'm you know how trying to get
it yeah well and that's the thing about
pursuing your dream is it's a long goal
man it's it's a long time and everything
it's what you're doing so it's like I
can understand that it felt like you're
like man what what could I do to help
right now but you got it on straight to
me man you're like all I can do to
really help it's not sabotage this
literally because like I said it in a
song the songs gone now but it was out
for a while I said in a song I was like
having conversations in my head it's
like my mom didn't even say it but like
in my head like I'm like you're freaking
out because it's like I'm out here I do
it for the fans like you do it for the
fan but you not at home and it's like
you just like in your head freaking out
like cuz you tell me so I'm doing this
like for damn and like we're getting
we're getting doing stuff it was like
but like today I was like ironing to see
like you know I mean and that's the
hardest thing that it's hard to there's
not one way to show up is the thing it
is like in times of tragedy especially
who we think that there's only one way
to show up it's like man I don't like I
don't know why but it just feel better
if you were here crying next to me right
right you want to physically like you
know yeah I mean in this you know that's
not unreasonable at all I really get
that man I'm you know I'm an emotional
person myself and definitely need some
but I mean it so it seems like we again
we talked on the way over it seems like
you guys are starting to near you know
processing things and yeah and in in
dealing with them and
and obviously like that's what's it's
chant kind of change in your music and
there's something I hear it a little bit
just in your newer songs obviously in
fake friends a little more vibe a little
laid-back I think that what's happening
coming forward though is it's definitely
gonna be probably probably what like
maybe a little more this healing out
loud so you guys went through this
tragedy indefinitely like what's uh
where you at now with this so now I mean
I mean recently really cuz I mean well
there was a bunch of stuff I mean a lot
of people hired I moved to Arizona I've
been out there now are you going through
a bunch of [__] and then I got crazy out
there just cuz it's a whole brand-new
set up and new parties and bigger cities
and right so like that so it got crazy
and I you know I kind of got out of
control a game but like in the in like
the recent like past six months
everything's kind of kind of like a
beautiful closure I guess yeah you know
I kind of like I mean I'm still having
fun everybody knows me I'm still having
fun and hanging out but like the like
the destruction is kind of like out of
my system I'm like we wrecked the cars
and went too far like plenty of times
now that it's like I kind of got to see
life differently yeah I mean especially
like you just you get different
perspectives that I mean a lot of it was
just like the ups and downs are so hard
to deal with because I mean you go from
being on tour and solo shows and
partying and like feeling like a
superstar every night and then like when
tour is over
and then like you just go home and like
sit at your house like it like just sit
at your house and like do nothing and
like I mean try to make music and like
keep being progressive and [__] but it's
it's just way different when you're at
home you know it doesn't feel like you
made it you know yeah you're like you
got to try to convince yourself that you
still as cool as you felt like man
that's something about like so like
touring so for my audio engineering job
like I tour tour just around the u.s.
here and there in certain periods and
it's
like for some reason that's kind of how
it happened for me it felt like when I
was out and about and posting about it
like on the gram stuff it felt like I
was like doing something I'm living like
this thing meet at the PD airport myself
but then you get back and you're you
know it's like [__] what like Who am I
what am I gonna do now we get confused
that we forget that like the whole thing
is your life the whole thing is the
process like remind yourself you're like
ya know before the toy like this is what
put me on like was sitting in my room
making music going crazy yeah like
you're just gonna keep doing it yes what
do you got let's let's talk mindset
where you at mine silhouette wise right
now like so obviously you know you're
still living your life like yeah you got
[__] under control you got the Beast
tamed I feel you've been working a lot
lately
what were you at right now like what's
your what's the vibe that you've been
putting out lately in your music like
like you said I kind of got to the point
where like the animal inside of me I can
like control it instead of like letting
it you know kind of ruin everything is
like when you can control it and channel
it in like direction that's when he gets
some crazy [__] so I've just kind of
been like channeling myself and just
making all this new music and is like
opened up a whole new chapter and kind
of like bringing stuff back from like
where I came from because you know I
love rap and hip-hop and all this new
[__] going on and whatnot but a lot of
what I grew up on was like guitars and
good grooves and hard rocking you know
all that craziness - so I've been
working on these are be like pop hip-hop
songs and like using those crazy bass
drums that we all love like 808 but then
you know like sitting like you know bass
guitar grooves and then rhythms with the
guitar and stuff I don't play the guitar
but you know I like working here but
working with people that be doing stuff
like that and like just putting like a
whole different part of my energy into
the music and then just I've been
writing way different
yeah I feel like I've been using my
words better alright yeah just like
learning more just like getting older
like as a man definitely I've been
feeling like that cuz I've definitely
been like feeling older lately and kind
of like looking back at my life and
seeing new perspectives and rather than
like being in the midst of doing what I
was doing I'm like looking at it and
seeing like why I was doing it and how I
was doing it and what I was necessarily
running towards or from or like what I
was dealing with so consciously that I
didn't even want to realize at the time
so it's just starting to like I mean to
see your own existence in a different
light you just start to learn about
yourself and when you know more about
yourself you can express it better
because right you did sometimes you
learn you learn about yourself as you're
expressing it like I have that sometimes
like a song was about and then all like
kind of add some lyrics to it like four
days this morning but I literally added
like two more lines to the [__] and I'm
like oh this song is about the Hat Emily
was like just right I thought I was
writing it because I've been working
with other pants I've been trying to get
more lyrics and [__] but so so this new
[__] like what are you discovering I
mean we we can we can dive into a couple
specific songs where you got like sit
down so when the fans here they already
know what it's about
yeah that's crazy you said that cuz like
for real like that's some real [__] like
I'll just be sitting there writing or
like sometimes I write and then I find
the beat or sometimes like like work
with we create a beat and then I read
the song into it or like I'll write the
song and then make a beat around it
sometimes I'll literally just walk in
there after like the songs they're just
like sing like and it'll just happen but
like sometimes dudes like you just be in
there and you're like writing and doing
all this stuff and you're just like yeah
this just sounds cool and then like you
come back two days later and you're like
damn this is about all these things yeah
you're like I think I'm gonna cry it
though like seriously that's one song it
was already out it's down it's coming
back like within a couple like a week or
so actually but if I die tomorrow that
song I was trying to write that song for
like
two years like just everything is about
but I didn't know how to like put it
together it was just kind of like I had
all these feelings and ideas about life
and like how I felt and stuff I guess
and that like I wanted to say and I
wanted to leave from our people and my
brothers and stuff like if I died
tomorrow like this is what I have to
tell you yeah and like I just always
wanted to ride it and like hey one day
like after two years I just walked over
to the microphone and I didn't mean to I
wasn't planning on it I was just like
I'm gonna freestyle to this beat and
just get my rhythms and see what I'm
thinking about and then I'll write over
that because I like to get that natural
feel out and I just walked up and just
sang the like the whole song just I just
I just like saying it it's just a clout
and like halfway through like I'm just
like like bawling like bawling just like
it's just like it was the most unreal
release I've ever expressively felt like
that that it was amazing damn bro that
because I mean it's about my dad and my
brothers and like my girlfriend and my
friends and just everyone I rolled yeah
just like my whole world like if like
this is how I feel like and you were
able to find anything yeah yeah and it
was it was so it was so crazy that's
such a special song to me yeah wait
what's the name if I die tomorrow it's
coming back out it's on the forever
it's a moment mixtape okay so I'm gonna
release this within a couple days maybe
today we'll see but what day does it
come out man I'm gonna try to drop it
like right before Christmas hopefully so
sad that's fine right because well right
now on Apple music
I took perfect timing where you want to
go and if I die tomorrow off because
they're being remastered and a lot of
people like those songs so yeah it's
perfect that those three are coming back
to Apple and Spotify so that'll be
that'll be cool okay [__] that's good to
know to you yeah damn but I mean we can
talk about new unreleased one though
because I got this new EP that
it might be held for a holdup what's a
TP ready listener who doesn't know is a
short compilation of songs that fit the
fit the vibe that not a whole album yeah
not a whole album is gonna be three
songs okay that's it
but the it's caught it's gonna be called
the 1988 EP and it's just uh it's gonna
be cool is gonna be a movie though oh
yeah so it's gonna be a movie
okay flirt all right give me a little
bit more than I got yeah so it's three
songs the first song is called I'm still
here okay oh my god yeah the first song
I'm still here the second song is called
smoke I've left sneak peeks of that
places and people like that one okay
smoke and then bad decisions in
parentheses 1988 and it's kind of like
you said it's kind of like me healing
out loud and understanding my mayhem and
that's what the movies gonna be about
it's gonna I don't know if I'm gonna
make it all three of the songs are gonna
be one movie or if it'll be a movie with
three episodes but regardless is equal
project though so what is gonna be we
started making it it's gonna be really
crazy dude I'm gonna have to after this
podcast I'm gonna have to like pack
right yeah I'll tell you a little piece
like it so I was gonna start out like in
a laboratory like it you know in like in
the spider-man movie like Green Goblin
like you sure like he's built in a
laboratory so it's gonna like somebody's
gonna walk in to this laboratory it's
gonna be all like dark and crazy and
shaytans gonna be in there working on
this thing working on this like
mutilated project and it's going to be
harsh 6:00 in the thing is the demented
project and so it's gonna be like this
because you know as an artist you
started to turn yourself into this
avatar like thing yeah like you bend and
into all these things so I was like
it'll be the mayhem of Shaytan almost
ruining it and filling ha she was a
little bit too much substances and
taking the girl away from him and then
how we react and it's gonna be like what
wait hold up hold up don't give it too
much that is so I'm so pumped up that I
feel that I respect you bro I love that
you're getting so much better at like
communicating you know because because
as an artist a lot of artists obviously
you you know there's a lot there's a
whole story in a whole world in your
head and you're like I think this is
important right I think that like I I
don't know exact what I'm trying to say
to you but there's a feeling that I
don't there's not really words for when
your whole life is just trying to get
out of the way or express away all right
right and that's like this movie is
literally gonna be like exactly what
I've wanted to say since I can ever
remember talking like right like
seriously like this movie is like it's
just me and how I feel about the world
dude let's talk about like aliases
because as you were saying that it's
pretty wild because I've actually been
I've been DJ Kronos for you know eight
years or something that's like how a lot
of people know who I am and I like over
the last year you know doing I mean I've
just been doing more audio engineering
audio directing work doing more
freelance stuff there but so I'm just
not doing as much DJing but I'm slowly
lately I'm just like I'm not really
wanting to DJ as much I'm just yeah I
enjoy the art of DJing but I'm just
doing less like public stuff I just want
to do less kind of dissolving Cronos is
what's happening well and so lately I've
been doing these sound art pieces and
just releasing them under those under
Jacob from the internet so it sounds
like kind of like yeah it seems like
we're kind of been doing a little bit
the same thing that like yeah I noticed
that you've been doing the Hashi six
things so dude I want to explain to you
know I always think of of course you're
gonna have hell of hands that are
listening to this but I always try to
remember like there might be a 45 year
old lady listening to this so I was like
playing like okay you had to break it
down for someone who like they're
confused about what you're doing but
like they want to understand right
aliases so like like explain those so
it's something you know this math
that we gotta wear and it represents
different parts of exactly because I
mean a lot of I mean a lot of my fans
don't know but a lot of my fans do not
like that there's been a couple versions
and that's kind of like what Hoshi 6
represents is you know different like
versions of me like coming through but I
mean it has always been me but of course
you you get to like different points and
it feels like you you know like you
evolve like different stages Lucian baby
exactly so like I started out as like
Hoshi won technically like the ocean for
people that knew about that and then
Hoshi 2 was me just being shading and
releasing music is that yeah and then
how III was like me like finally like
making something that like broke through
to the public and like what time was
talking 3 ah like what song can probably
like said you said we couldn't when like
I got a song with mark bottles like that
first yeah thing and people would like
because I was like the first time ever
that people were like woah we're gonna
take him seriously and like it might do
something and it was kind of like a wild
stage of like for the first time like
okay we've just been in our bedroom with
me and my little brother just making a
bunch of crazy [__] for fun because we
thought that we sounded crazy yeah and
just having fun and like dropping stuff
and then all of a sudden it was like
people were listening and like waiting
for what was gonna happen next and it
was like whoa this is and this is a
little bit different like I think you're
like yeah dude all set and you're like
oh we gotta do something yeah okay so
now like we actually have to do
something cool so then it was like I
feel like the fourth version was kind of
like my dread head version like doing
like wake up and yeah yeah and me kind
of like finding a sound and like you
know really breaking through to the fans
and going on tour and
having all that fun and stuff and then I
say like the v like a section of it I
mean at this time I was just Hoshi like
through the whole thing but like quick I
like because like there was a early like
spark and feeling and like because I
felt completely different two sections
of my career like so the Fez was like
right after we lost pops and then like
had to come home and like still be like
this thing that I had created yeah but I
have to deal with everything at the same
time and like is like honestly like I
just had like this brand-new life
already and then like coming home and
didn't like that all happening it was
like everything in my life changed at
that point like every single thing that
I knew it was different so just like it
was just like this whole new thing and
then finally I got to like what we're
getting and understanding and started to
understand like what I'm supposed to
mean in the world at least to myself and
what I want to do and say and feel and
like what I want to leave behind because
what I'm realizing it's like musics like
the one thing in the world is like when
I'm gone it it's here and that's like
that's me it's like they can't take you
away you know it's like I get to say
that forever right here on one that is
like I got my dad's ashes and this
forever because it's like what what you
leave the harness forever and like I
want to leave something that's important
so that's like my birthday is December 6
and happy belated baby thank you thank
you this is like the sixth version of me
like I understand it myself
obviously I love Nikki Sixx and like his
writing and how like has met him like he
avoided death million times and I just
like let his chaos like feeling my stuff
so I mean just like I got it like a lot
of six inspiration I guess so that's
like this new version is just kind of
like me just being me but like finally
for the first time like I've been trying
to be this forever but it's just
especially in music you got to learn so
much and like
be able to even creatively do certain
things so like with these guitars and
like how I'm making music and how I'm
sounding and how I'm singing cuz I mean
I'm not like a great singer like I had
to really try like born Beyonce we talk
like I'm not even I'm still not even
like a good singer but like to even get
to like where I like how like this
little sound is yeah like it took a lot
in a long time and a lot of finessing
and working and a lot of everything
mhm so like for the first time now like
with this new music I feel like it's not
me searching and trying to figure out
what I'm supposed to make or how I'm
supposed to make it or what I'm supposed
to do it's like I know what I'm supposed
to what I want to say I guess and how I
want to say it and I know how I feel now
like I'm not like as lost in it so now I
just like go in there and say it I guess
yeah the music is I don't know how to
explain it I guess it's kind of like
learning how to be your real self no
literally cuz I mean the world makes you
feel crazy yes
so I mean for a long time like I thought
that like this mayhem and there's a
weird person that I am like because I
mean a lot of people think I'm just
really cool or whatever you believe that
is like I'm just really weird now I've
always felt really weird about the world
like you know makes you feel like
there's a certain size of you that you
shouldn't show or that you should be
ashamed of where the
you should keep to yourself or whatever
it may be in our town - yeah especially
coming from a small town where hill town
exactly you do something and everybody
knows about it neither they they're
applauding you forward of the laughing
at you for you so it's like you kind of
got to commit to whatever you show to
the public where we're from so I've
always been like now that I I love being
me and the people that are close you
know I always had me to the death but
like at least what I've shown to the
public it's it's scary
because you gotta wear that like you
said like a mask you know you gotta wear
that and they only understand what you
show them or the image that little peep
into their life they see that's all you
get to be for a little bit so it's
really scary when you go to show people
stuff yeah so like finally get into this
point where I'm understanding it and I
can just kind of express it and I'm okay
with it yeah it's like it's a little bit
of a weight off my shoulders so now it's
like we just gotta figure out the market
to the next that's it that [__] is that
that'll come by the wayside yeah that'll
happen with time that [__] that you just
keep learning it like all then we got a
I [__] technology that'll take it over
right you're ready to get further right
baby
yeah no but yeah that's that's tight I
really like your perspective on that it
seems kind of you know I haven't seen
you for a bit you know so I'm just
pumped to see anyway but it does seem
like your vibe is is right man it seems
like the glow in your eyes is back thank
you I appreciate that that means a lot
does is important you say that cuz
that's literally what scared me is like
when I was at a point that I was just
like self-destructing without even
realizing that I was trying to just kill
myself like pray I'd like looked in the
mirror one day and like my eyes just
looked so dead and then I was just like
whoa I mean like I'm like an
off-the-wall excited person and I just
looked like I was just dragging myself
through life and I was like yeah we got
to change that like I'm supposed to like
Hashi
hey this is important for a lot of
people that don't know Hashi and my
Native American language means sunshine
a rising shuttin so that's when I didn't
see that gloves like I'm supposed to be
shining like that's why my music I want
to say to stuff because I want to light
the way for people that go through the
[__] I go through that we can get it
we're gonna be okay failing out loud man
yeah I'm all about that yeah I love that
bro I feel like your fans definitely
[__] feel hey we were just talking
about how like you met up you're like
dropping off a hoodie yourself or
dropping by a fan and she didn't know
that you're gonna be there right yeah
her mom's surprise there and she's like
I don't know it was it was a good
feeling she didn't know I was coming she
jumped out the car screaming and she it
was it was an experience like when fans
get that excited to see me like it it
blows my mind because I just feel like a
kid that especially I get my own town
like I'm a kid that just like walked
around these streets and skated around
these streets and you know like this is
just mind-blowing when I don't know my
city and they recognize me for something
I guess yeah they think they're meeting
a superstar and you're just like I'm
just I'm just a guy like in your so
humbled bro you told me about a couple
things like that like your fans already
[__] appreciate what you're doing
that they know what you're saying and
then just by being yourself
authentically it's it's coming across
and that's the best thing like you know
like we said we grew up in a town where
it's it's hard to be yourself like it's
just super and it's you know it's I
[__] love it here but when you're
young and you're wearing tight pants you
get me know it's how it's been bro I
grew up wearing tight pants a couple
years ahead of you so I know exactly how
I came into my freshman year they didn't
even I was small but like I'm tall now
I'm like 6 1 but like like back then my
freshman year I was 5 foot tall shorter
than all the girls and I walked in that
[__] wearing hot pink Roxie skinny
jeans that were all torn because I
didn't even have a size that fit me and
the guys who'd you get those Roxy's from
like a girl you know I was a store my
momma got him Oh
I always loved it I was just out here
trying to be a punk I wonder if I was
working at the stores that you came into
got there because like I worked it to
the wall stores and I would just sell
kids I'm like yeah bro that's where that
was my first shot was back then
yeah I was just trying to make noise
that's what I mean that's what I like it
turned into music cuz it was just like
I've always had that expressive side and
I just have always wanted to make noise
and like you know I like I just like
having fun and like expressing and the
eunich evening you are at your club
exactly just whatever it is like art to
me is like so important and life
definitely art to you - exactly exactly
yeah that's like so I mean you can see
my style like almost like what I'm
feeling or going through like about how
I'm dressed I mean my style has changed
I mean somewhat dramatically through my
whole career I guess like it's grown
with me I feel like and I mean some
people may not like it because it's
getting crazy but we don't like it they
way I love it it's so fun like yeah you
can kind of like in that I mean I guess
that's why I like my fashion lately has
been getting a lot more crazy cuz like I
was saying it's like I'm getting so much
more okay with just being me yeah it's
like before it was like I said it's
scary to show the public like are they
gonna be okay with it like yeah and then
it's confusing cuz you're like is this
the real me or like alright make you
feel uncomfortable like bro you're
changing like that was the hardest thing
for me like coming home from tour that's
corny and then everybody was like you're
changing you're acting different and I
was like did you do this [__] to stay
the same I was like I don't want to like
be the same guy like forever I was like
when I kind of get boring like I was
like imma treat everybody the same and
I'ma be me and rock with that and like
Who I am as a loving person yes all that
has of you and everybody wants to
question you when you start progressing
because they start feeling uncomfortable
about it so then you start questioning
yourself like you said is this the real
me or am I just being weird or am I
doing this or
am I trying to get attention am I trying
to like make sure I'm known I always
thought about that man I love fashion I
always have in like I go through all
these struggles of like like myself hate
would come back hard when sometimes I'd
be wearing like this exuberant outfit
that I would leave the house you know
just like Kirchhoff yeah you having so
much bro and somebody makes me feel
stupid or someone points it out or even
just nobody does and I just all of a
sudden get like what am i doing like I'm
trying to get attention here and then I
start hating myself it's a weird bro
this is corny and then you're like no
like it's not it's not dumb to have fun
that gets fun likes press yourself
like I mean a lot of times I like
wearing just sweats and a hoodie and
just being comfy as [__] and like
rocking but like every more so like like
when you dress up and like put your
thing together like how you're feeling
like it's so fun like and it you feel
like as you but yeah like there's a lot
of haters they get up they're like point
something out and then you just like I
started thinking yeah that's always
behind [__] too but I'm Way too high
everybody's looking at me right now
that's the realest thing wait hold up
you know what I did when I had first
started like smoking 10:08 is I was like
I'm gonna do the ultimate like I'm gonna
go into public heart I went to a hockey
game high as a kite it's the whitest
brightest lightest thing you've ever
experienced yeah but but anyway yeah
don't go and high in public trying to
[__] express yourself it's like man
all right I was trying to just be in my
whole world that's what now well that's
the thing for me is like I really don't
care what people think at all it's just
uh like I'm either like anti-social are
very social I'm gonna have like two
modes so like sometimes it's kind of
like hard for me I talk to people
especially when they make me question
something so I guess somebody like walks
up like what the [__] up with those
pants bro like I could really care less
what they think about my pants but when
I have to like trying to sit there and
like they just thinking about a question
answer yeah
I think and then I just feel awkward cuz
like I really don't know what to say
like this is just weird like I just
rather be vibing so yeah dude all right
so so listeners if you're listening and
people address exuberantly or someone
just something crazy realize that your
very first reaction sometimes what they
mean I think is like I noticed that
you're like yours your outfit is loud
and I just kind of wanted to say that to
you yeah language work so I think you
know listeners if you see if someone
who's wearing an outfit that's just
crazy just to understand that it's a
little bit of like an interior of
they're just spoken through so they're
probably an interesting wonderful person
that's how that's kind of a little
secret like it's like when someone if
they have like dope clean shoes or
they're just like their outfits super
normal and then have these out-of-town
shoes have these you know or like
they're we're in a leather jacket it's
like you show me the only leather jacket
I'm like yeah what's that what's up with
you something I want to make sure we do
is I want to talk about your influences
man like I know that like because I
think we met we were talking about we
met back in the days of like in g e--'s
yeah yeah yeah we met but I remember
that we would like sense be easy [__]
back and then I know I know you love
caddy you want to talk about some of
your influences and then also like like
who were so most of them and the
influences that you've been working with
- okay so I mean growing up I think a
lot of my music was like my dad's music
I mean early on but like one of the
first people is good certain ladies but
I guess it might explain why I'm easy
kind of nether and Jack Johnson it's
like one of like my early like most
favorite artists ever and like his means
it's just like super beautiful
it's like untouchable so like there was
a lot of that and then like Red Hot
Chili Peppers was always like super dope
stuff like that and then I started
liking my own types of music as I got
older who got you in the hip hop um
I think honestly just like being a
school and being a skater and like being
a like a punk like you're like just like
fine in my style so like that's like
when I was in a pumpkin and
yeah cuz I guess yeah if we're going in
order it went from like that to where
like we were wearing zebra print skinny
jeans in middle school and being a
skater and like dyeing her hair and
listen and Motley Crue and like suicide
silence and like crazy ass baby just
like just being crazy and then from that
it was like okay well like this is
really fun but like I kind of just
wanted to like fit in a little bit like
so and then like I started listening to
hip-hop which was super dope and like I
think my first favorite rapper probably
is like Lil Wayne like t-pain yeah
because like I always loved like the
auto-tune sound early on just because it
was his hella melodic I love melody as I
love that whole sort of deal so I like
that and then but that was just really
like what was available to me I didn't
understand music at that point or like
you know so people started sending me
stuff showing me [__] and then so like
early in middle school is what I found
Kid Cudi and Wiz Khalifa and those are
probably like mutt to my favorite
artists and yeah like those two what
albums was it like you remember like
what song I was like it's like day and
night time nice day or night with Kid
Cudi but like right before that he had
like Cleveland is dope like some of
those early songs but they like Wiz
Khalifa cabin fever like before that
like what was their cushion orange juice
all that's I got trouble in middle
school because I was always like
slapping cushion orange juice and like
all the weed songs and stuff like that
yeah yeah I was like I loved that [__] I
loved that vibe that was such a dope
time for music I feel like the I feel
like that that genre of music that time
that little chunk of music whenever what
you have were years that was I have like
some homies that I can just think of
instantly right it's time I'll just be
on me and my friends like like right
after like eighth grade freshman year
sophomore year we just be on datpiff
calm right downloading all the Wiz
Khalifa mixtapes all like Tyga well done
two and three listen to the most
he should we could getting all the Mac
Miller mixtapes like that piff was the
spot I was like before SoundCloud was
open
that was what dude yeah that was for
hip-hop man yeah I just I just download
all that [__] on my iPod and then when I
got my first whip I didn't even have
that good what was your first whip Honda
cr-v yeah like that 99 you know yeah so
I had that but it just had a CD player
in it so we go on datpiff and download
all that [__] we burned like all the was
Khalifa mixtapes all the like [__] so we
just sit in the car just slap of that
[__] forever that was the only thing
that played in my car for like four
years just was Khalifa
it was crazy though bro it probably
trained your brain to be a good rapper
like 20-acre it was like like that was
that was really my favorite mixtape that
was later on like my senior year we had
actually yeah like my senior year are
the only things that we listen to assure
you not we'd listen to the acid rap
mixtape and 28 grams by Wiz Khalifa that
is like what what so 28 grants are
trying to think what something else oh
it's just a mixtape it's got like banger
foreign oh [__] man like that weed makes
it's like a bunch of remixes to like pop
songs like but it's called trap Wiz and
like it's just like him going crazy and
like singing like crazy auto-tune song
which music think about how much [__]
that dudes put out dude I have an ipod
an iPod Nano one of them blue ones that
I got my sophomore year I still have it
and I literally and this just old I have
like 380 Wiz Khalifa songs on that I'm
not even joking he's unstoppable like
yeah I'm like anything he still just
jobs mixtape you have a couple months
again you know fast and furious yeah he
doesn't have to do anything anymore dude
yeah he's broke he probably has like
Bill Murray he apparently has like one
[__] phone and you just mute miss
sometimes the answer sometimes he has it
I bet he was Khalifa's like that it's
like if you want to feature with Wiz he
just like once a month he picks up his
phone and he's like yeah
oh fast and furious now do mangy nah
yeah I'm good I'm good
so you drew inspiration from those guys
a lot you have been let's let's make
sure recover you know you have a lot of
features right you you know like I've
been with you down in in in Portland
working with jury you know I can in work
in them with laying down there
definitely definitely been working with
like what's you got any like news coming
up with with music with with labels any
of that kind of [__] going on kinda I
mean we always make a music with it with
the boys late always kids he goes down
on the rap in exact spitting as I've
been doing a lot of cool [__] he's got a
crazy studio set up now but uh I got I
probably got more features coming with
DC cap things on perfect timing that's
literally like that's probably my
favorite portlet rapper that is crazy
DC yeah he's got he's got subject more
of his stuff out he's got some like some
of his solo stuff in his new studies
doing right now is super dope I've been
I've been loving it his music is so sick
and like he's such a dope dude man every
time we can't we just get along and just
[__] [__] up have a good last time like
he's super cool his musics tight we
always working on some new projects so I
got I'm working with this guy also from
Phoenix his name's réal Wylie he's crazy
like pop R&B sing and he just got off
tour he's doing a lot of really really
dope [__] he's like on his own level
like he's he's who inspired me just like
performing with a band again because
like he invited me to some shows I was
performing with them and he performs
with a band like full band and [__] and
a DJ and it's just like the craziest set
of sounds man it was so tight and then I
started like doing that like having a
drummer behind me and a guitar and a lot
of my songs like that anyways and I was
just I fell in love with it it's so much
more real and like the fans love it
because I don't have to just stare at
you walking back and forth across the
stage yeah they get something to watch
that they can zone out different people
and exactly exactly because the people
that bounce can
pounds and the people that just want to
find can watch the guitar player and
just kind of Bob like there's some
there's some spiritual magical [__]
happening when more than one person is
contributing to the do its I have a
sensing it lately with these new bands
that is way more energy man it's like
movies it's hard to like give that much
of your energy to the people when you're
on stage so like when there's that much
more people it's like you are sharing it
like it's like a super team like yeah
it's great it is a super team I mean
that's that's the thing is you're kind
of the maestro bro that's the thing is
as you're getting better as you're
improving you know like you're gonna be
learning you've been learning a lot of
instruments like trying to and yeah I've
known that so I don't know just think
about in 10 15 20 years like what what's
gonna happen you know you're gonna
actually I want to to really you know
have be the maestro of the audience and
all these ways yeah absolutely that's
what I'm really excited actually is cuz
I've been talking about at least with
David the guy who plays a guitar with me
David Robinson yes bro it's so cool I've
been like singing him around in the
circles that like with the bands yeah
grew up with his older brother over me
and his older brother
we would like DJ like the renegade
parties or that service yeah David's
awesome his everything about that dude
is crazy dope yeah he's got a vibe
though we've been talking because to me
I'm like it's about to be 2020 and like
I think that's really important just
because if you think about it like music
changes every decade like there's like
every every decade is like for art in
general is monumental yeah like that's
how you'd like there's a 70s to 60s 80's
and 90's like to thousands like there's
it there's it means something I don't
know like that's like I feel like the
20s I'm like especially because if you
look right now an art like a lot of
things are being remade right now like
movies are a lot of remakes and like
there's a lot of the stories that are
being remade and resampled and like all
that stuff like that were kind of at
like a creative block right now just
Humanity in some sorts of sense like I
mean we're definitely doing a lot of new
[__] but like in some ways like it is
kind of like we're hitting a wall we're
running out of things that do so I feel
like in
like this new decade here like musics
about to do something crazy there's
gonna be some butterfly [__] happen yeah
I don't know what it is I've literally
been saying I was like I don't know what
it is
but we need to be a part of it how does
it say you're like a part of it yeah I
mean lately I've been I've been kind of
expanding like what I want to do because
I don't want to completely stop
detangling right I love you know not so
much performing and it's I don't know
creating something from start to finish
obviously but I I'm just kind of curious
where mine's gonna go I want to start
doing more more MIDI work and stuff too
so I know that's kind of like my realm
of what happens with a DJ I started
doing more MIDI work and [__] and then
your realm you start even starting to do
more on instrumentation definitely and
all that so all right well we got a we
got to wrap it up here shortly
if there's anything else you want to
mention I definitely want to end on a
message to the fans I know that like the
fans like the people who listen to music
the people who support you as something
you and I always talk about you're like
one of us appreciative grateful [__]
people that I know thank you there's a
lot to me yeah dude I mean your fans
mean a lot to you and you make that a
parent so I mean is there any messages
you want to end with like to them like
anything maybe whatever how about this
what if they're going through some
mayhem the other time in their life like
you got any messages for them man
everything is temporary that's like I
got forever on my neck but like
everything's temporary I mean it's like
life gets really hard and life gets
really great but one thing you got to
know is none of it's gonna last forever
you just gotta like ride whatever's in
front of you and I mean you can make it
as good or better as you want
I mean I've I've honestly been in some
of the worst times in my life having the
most fun in my life just because you're
just fighting through and just going
hard like and I've had times where like
everything was great in my life and I
felt worse than ever
just because like you're in a weird bug
like it it just depends on how are you
gonna deal with it and that's what like
I mean I was taught that by a coach a
long time ago like it's like
everything's a mentality is how you
gonna treat it how are you gonna
approach it like as a perspective like
I had it like like a terrible trip one
time and everything got so dark and just
like life was at the time it was just so
dark so dark and like I couldn't see
anything good in the world or in the
room at the time and just like the only
thought that I could have in my head was
job butterflies on the wall and I was
like it was like I don't know why but
that's all I could think about so I just
grabbed a marker and just started
drawing butterflies and like [__] all
over the wall because it was like it's
dark I was like I'm the only one that
can make it light and like butterflies
are pretty so like I'm gonna just start
drawing [__] you just got out of the way
and let your hand yeah like exactly like
you just kind of like and I mean that's
kind of that's just how I thought about
life after that is like if you want it
to be pretty make it pretty if you keep
complaining I mean it's easy to complain
and stuff and I'll do it plenty but like
it's easy to complain it's easy to talk
yourself into a dark terrible place and
it's easy to get stuck there cuz it's
really hard to get out but if you want
to you're you're the one that can do it
and that's like that's why I make music
because it's like Kid Cudi to me was
like a superhero and he made me feel
like I wasn't alone when I had to fight
these battles and then like slowly like
you get like when I started making music
and stuff I wanted I wanted a superhero
I like I needed somebody to tell me
something like so that I could feel okay
and then I realized like nobody's gonna
tell me that nobody's gonna say and then
I was like well I'm gonna just sing it
and that's why like I literally started
making music so that I could sing it and
listen to it for myself because made me
feel better like that was really it like
so I'll just go say whatever I needed to
hear and then I realized I was like
other people need to hear that like so
that so that we can all feel okay cuz
it's really gonna be okay you know I
mean it like it sucks sometimes but it's
gonna be okay like he's gotta keep
moving and making better choices you
don't like something then just change it
like change isn't always easy but it's
easier than being in a place you don't
want to be yeah you don't have to stick
in that place you want to be it's crazy
I mean I think it's something we don't
really realize when we're in these
darkness and we think they're just like
we have to stay in here we deserve to be
in here what
right right but what what the thing is I
was just thinking as you're saying about
the money my man that dark place that
you're in right now that's just the kid
that's sorry that exactly bro that's
just the cocoon that exactly and that's
how I've always kind of felt is like a
massage at Aries and like I definitely
like you don't even gotta believe in
astrology or whatever but like my
personality is like a Sagittarius it's
like a shoot for the stars we want to be
free we don't like being controlled we
just won't go for it that's it and
that's it like I was like if you're
shooting for the stars you got to pull
back before you shoot the arrow like you
have to pull back some tension yeah yeah
so every time like me it's funny cuz
like like people around me all think
that it's weird because when things
start getting really tough or I start
getting into a weird spot with music or
I start getting like frustrated I don't
know what's next I'm always like oh this
is about to be crazy like cuz when I
don't know what's coming next
I'm like it's about to be like that just
means I get to hit another breakthrough
like it's cool when you're doing it and
you know what you're doing and having a
good time but it's it's temporary
because eventually that idea is gonna
run out and you're gonna have to do
something different so then when I get
in that in-between and I'm stuck it's
kind of frustrating but I get so excited
because I'm like eventually I'm about to
break through and I'm about to start
doing something right completely new and
that's gonna be exciting again like
wouldn't be able to even see that path
lit up at all if you weren't doing that
if you were just again this sucks I'm so
anxious I'm so stressed out whatever it
exactly move it forward but that's and
then eventually you just let it go and
you ain't doing nothing and you there so
I was like do something man exactly no
matter what it is in life like it
doesn't got to be what I'm doing it
doesn't gotta be what anybody even
thinks you should be doing like whatever
you feel like your heart wants to do
just take off running in that direction
and when you hit obstacles like just
don't don't just punch it over and over
sometimes its way around like yeah
sometimes these guys think it over that
obstacle are going to come up like you
don't have them right now but
need to worry about that right exactly
when that obstacle comes up you're gonna
be able to find exact stay on and I'm so
happy you came here today all right
let's just end off with with tell
everybody where to find you and then
tell everybody what's coming up next
alright you can find me on instagram @
hv shi hoshi you can find me on Apple
music Spotify SoundCloud YouTube all
that good stuff
thank you to all my fans love you guys
for real for real
we're gonna keep riding through this
[__] we got a lot of great stuff coming
we got I just found a new music video
for fake friends while I'm here so
that's gonna be coming soon and it's
gonna be really really wild and then we
got that EP and a couple more singles
coming mmm new a lot of new things for
2020 they're gonna be really big but I
don't want to say nothing cuz it's
really like when it happens it's really
gonna shock people it's gonna be crazy
well bro I'm happy to [__] be on that
path you man I'm here and I'm happy I'm
happy that your fans finally got to like
hear you speak for a little bit but
really I've just been talking through
the music for so long so I'm grateful
that you let me come in here and [__]
don't talk about my heart though to
other people how it is and yeah open up
a little bit yeah I mean that's the
thing is I mean I know your music but I
need before you music and so I know you
I know you for your heart so that's what
I want to make sure that people
understand about you I appreciate that
for there's a lot of course man all
right man drunk I love podcasts out
you